HUY DO

RUBY ON RAILS WEB DEVLOPER



I really love being a web developer.

Currently, I'm working with Rails but still open for any chances to learning new things related to web development

PERSONALITY HIGHLIGHTS

- Motivated by problem solving
- Independent worker
- Works well with deadlines
- Collaborative and efficient
- Love sharing knowledge

CONTACT DETAILS

Address:

E Home S Department, District 9, Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

Email:

huydo91@outlook.com

Phone:

+84 869 112601

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/huy-do-772b32143

Blog:

https://jackiedo91.github.io/jackie_do_blog/

BASIC INFORMATION

Just a guy has a little passion to build wonderful websites, delivery the best quality to customers.

I'm a Ruby on Rails web developer with almost 2 years of experience in various fields of web development: Frontend, Back-end and Server Administration.

Like challenging myself, dare to take responsibilities, enjoy coding and learning new things everyday.

"Keep doing it while your eyes and hands can handle. Sooner or later one of the two will fail you and that work will be a great reminder of just how much talent you gave the world."

EDUCATION

University of Science — Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam (2010 - 2014)

Bachelor Degree in Software Development

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

* Web Developer, NUS Technology, VietNam (Sep 2016 - Present)

Working as a Ruby on Rails web developer, cooperate with BA and other developers to analyze and convert client's idea to requirements, build new features and maintain existing features.

* Professional Analyst Programmer, CSC, VietNam (Jan 2015 - Aug 2016).

Analyzing business requirements from Singapore clients and transform to technical specifications
Working alongside other developers to maintain and implement a huge system in various fields of Insurance industry.

Have worked onsite in Singapore to go live the product of Tokio Marine Singapore.

PROJECTS

BOX AT WORK

Website:

SEP 2016 - PRESENT

https://www.boxie24.com/ https://www.boxatwork.com/

This is a Germany startup that supply storage services in 16 cities in Germany, France, Netherlands and United States. It received Series A funding of € 5,5 million, and leading on-demand Self Storage platform.

I'm working on both backend and frontend for developing new features and maintain the current website (focus on payment system). I also have to deploy and monitor the server.

Rails 4.2 Ruby 2.2 PostgreSQL CoffeeScript HAML Bootstrap

TECHNICAL STACK

Elastic Search Capistrano Adyen Payment Platform Mailgun

IAMIP (INVENTION) Website:

https://www.iamip.com/

DEC 2017 - JAN 2018

This is a one sub program of a management system used for managing ideas and inventions. The whole system is built on many platforms, but i just worked on the sub program implemented by Rails RESTful API for correcting business logic and fix some minor functions in back end.

TECHNICAL STACK

Rails 5.1 Ruby 2.4 RESTful API PostgreSQL ReactJS

SKILLS

LANGUAGE: English - Intermediate

TECHNICAL SKILLS: Rails Ruby HAML Bootstrap HTML5/CSS3 CoffeeScriipt Javascript

PostgreSQL Redis

Git Capistrano